COREY HAMAT

Front-End Web Developer

CONTACT

coreyhamat@gmail.com

(647) 998 - 1981

www.coreyhamat.me

Toronto, ON

SKILLS

WEB DEVELOPMENT:

HTML5 | CSS3 | SCSS | JavaScript (ES6+) | jQuery | RESTful APIs | Firebase | React | Building Accessible Websites | Version Control | Git & GitHub | Paired Programming | Teambased Development | Project Scope Management

CREATIVE SKILLS:

Vectorworks | Adobe InDesign | Adobe Photoshop | Adobe XD

EDUCATION

JUNO COLLEGE OF TECHNOLOGY

2021

- Web Development Immersive Certificate
- Web Development Con-Ed
- · Accelerated JavaScript

RYERSON SCHOOL OF PERFORMANCE

2014 - 2020

Completed 39 credits towards BFA in Performance Production

ABOUT

I enjoy building websites that focus on accessibility & responsiveness. I have prior experience in technical theatre, and have developed a sharp attention to detail & excellent communication skills. I bring the ability to work directly with clients, listen to their needs attentively, and bring their vision for the project to life!

PROJECTS:

PERFECT PLAYLIST PROCUREMENT

GIT REPO | LIVE

React | RESTful API | SASS | Firebase

Using Deezer's API, a user adds a random song from a selected artist to a global playlist. Users can search for artists by genre, or by searching for their name

THE DIGITAL CINEPHILE

GIT REPO | LIVE

HTML | SASS | CSS | JavaScript

A movie/TV recommendation app, built with the TMDB API, which displays a gallery of recommended movies and/or TV Shows based on user input. The website uses multiple API calls to display each recommended film's/TV Show's poster, official trailer (if available), user rating, and plot overview.

THE NYGMA MACHINE

GIT REPO | LIVE

React | RESTful API | SASS | Firebase

A randomly generated maze game that, when completed, shares a piece of advice, provided by the AdviceSlip API, based on a keyword selected by the user. The user earns a score, based on the number of steps they take to complete the maze, and the difficulty they selected, which is either displayed on a "Hall of Fame" or "Hall of Shame"

EXPERIENCE

USHER - ED MIRVISH & CAA THEATRE

Ed Mirvish Enterprises Itd | Sept 2019 - Mar 2020

Maintained a welcoming environment by positively engaging with over 100 patrons
per performance, communicating important information to the audience, and
resolving any conflicts or issues that a patron might encounter.

SOUND DESIGNER - THE SEVENTH SEAL

Ryerson School of Performance | Winter 2017

• Collaborated with the director to develop a live (foley) soundscape for the production. Tested various household objects and instruments to accurately recreate the director's desired sound effects.

OFFICE ASSISTANT

Vaughan Pediatric Clinic | May 2012 - August 2015

Aided with developing the clinic's digital face by scanning the patients' files into a
digital library, performing regular maintenance on the clinic's website via
 Wordpress, and assisting with the development of their social media presence.